在最初
在六个奇异点和创世黎明之前
天神族至尊阿里瑟姆便已出现
创造了第一个太阳 将光带入宇宙
生命开始蓬勃发展 万物处于平衡
直到一种不自然的掠食物种出现
以智慧生命为食
它们叫变异族 宇宙因而陷入浑沌
为了恢复自然秩序
阿里瑟姆派出永恒族
来自奥林匹亚星的不死英雄
歼灭变异族
永恒族原本对阿里瑟姆深信不疑
直到永恒族至尊艾贾克
所领导的一项任务改变了一切
双语合并：风吹来的那片云
支持我们，欢迎购买VIP移除所有广告，具体：www.OpenSubtitles.org
时候到了
It is time.
很美吧
It's beautiful, isn't it?
我是伊卡利斯
I'm Ikaris.
我是瑟希
I'm Sersi.
（公元前5000年）
（美索不达米亚）
它来了 快跑
It's coming! Run!
父亲
Father!
快跑
Run!
好身手
Good fight.
彼此彼此
You, too.
谢谢你 艾贾克
Thank you, Ajak.
（今日 伦敦）
（形塑人类历史的文物）
（提醒 上午9点）
惨了
Shit.
借过…
Excuse me. Excuse me.
我知道我迟到了 查理
I know I'm late, Charlie.
（查尔斯达尔文）
「在我们广阔的地球上
"In this broad Earth of ours,
在无数的污秽与火山渣之间
"Amid the measureless grossness and the slag,
安定尘封于地心之中
"Enclosed and safe within its central heart,
完美的种子静静窝藏」
"Nestles the seed Perfection."
这位诗人对人性的希望和乐观
The poet's hope and optimism in humanity
呼应我们最近的胜利 一半人口回归
echoes our recent universal victory, the return of half our population...
感谢老天 她来了
And, thank God, there she is.
我们杰出的博物馆科学家 瑟希小姐
Our brilliant museum scientist, Ms. Sersi, the person who will be
她今天应该为各位同学上课
and was always supposed to be giving you your presentation today.
谢谢惠特曼先生 抱歉我迟到了
Thank you, Mr. Whitman. Sorry I'm late, everyone.
今天我们要学顶级掠食者
Today, we'll be learning about the importance
在平衡生态系中的重要性
of apex predators in a balanced ecosystem.
念诗
Poetry?
我不知该说什么 这些孩子让我紧张
I completely ran out of things to say, and these kids make me nervous.
我觉得你很迷人 教授
Well, I thought you were very charming, Professor.
晚上见
See you tonight.
唷 晚上见
Ooh! "See you tonight."
好了 安静
All right, settle down.
所以…
So...
谁能告诉我什么是顶级掠食者
who can tell me what an apex predator is?
追捕猎物为食的动物
Animals that hunt their prey for food.
非常好
Very good.
顶级掠食者像其他掠食者一样猎食
Apex predators do hunt their prey for food, like all predators.
但它们有一点与众不同
But one thing that sets them apart
栖地中没有其他动物强到能猎杀它们
is that there are no other animals in their habitat strong enough to hunt them.
谁能给我举个例子
Who can give me an example?
狮子
Lions.
狼　-没错
- Wolves. - Correct.
地震
Earthquake.
蹲下…
Get down. Get down!
是地震 蹲在桌子底下
It's an earthquake, everyone. Get down!
躲在桌子底下
Under the tables!
我帮你 放心 很快就过去了
Let me help you. Don't worry, it'll pass soon.
没关系 过来
It's all right. Come here.
没事了…
You're all right. You're all right.
我喜欢这首歌
I like this song.
我也是
Me, too.
想跳舞吗
Do you wanna dance?
怎么搞的
Wait, what the hell?
你的手
Your hand!
你喝太多了 我该走了
You've had too much to drink. I gotta go.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐 亲爱的戴恩
Happy birthday, dear Dane
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
恭喜　-哦耶
- Hip, hip! - Hooray!
这是中世纪的吗
Is this from the Middle Ages?
有你的家族徽章
It has your family crest.
一定很贵吧
It must have cost a fortune.
我是网络下标高手
I'm a good eBay bidder.
谢谢
Thank you.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
所以你有考虑过同居的事吗
So, have you given any more thought to us moving in together?
有 我考虑过了
Yeah, I... I thought about it.
我不能搬去和你住
I can't move in with you.
我也觉得你会这么说
Yeah. Thought you'd say that.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我想我知道为什么
And I think I know why.
你是巫师吗
Are you a wizard?
什么
What?
对 就像奇异博士
Yeah, like Doctor Strange.
不 我…
No. I'm...
我发现在你身边时会发生不寻常的事
I've noticed some unusual things happen when I'm around you.
例如服务生不理我们 水就变成咖啡
Like our water always turns to coffee whenever the waiter ignores us.
因为你对咖啡因上瘾了
That's your caffeine addiction talking.
丝派克也会透露口风
And Sprite says things...
像你和前男友在一世纪前分手
...like you and your ex-boyfriend broke up a century ago.
她说的
She said that?
而且他会飞
And he can fly.
他是飞行员
He's a pilot.
去开房间啦
Get a room, you two.
能走了吗 我睡觉时间过了
Can we go now? It's past my bedtime.
你真的恋爱了吗
Are you really in love?
如果是呢
What if I am?
那你最好跟他说实话
You better tell him the truth, then.
我会找机会
I'm working on it.
你们想吃披萨吗
You guys wanna get pizza?
不了 谢谢
No, thank you!
他不会长生不老 和他同居吧
He won't live forever, you know. Move in with him.
我跟你一起住啊
I live with you.
戴恩
Dane.
靠 那是变异族吗
Shit! Is that a Deviant?
戴恩 快跑
Dane, run!
瑟希 　-我们走
Sersi? Let's go.
那是什么东西 　-变异族
What is that thing? A Deviant!
你说你们杀光它们了
You said you killed them all!
你跟他说的
You told him that?
你相信我 　-现在信了
You believed me? I do now!
你想干嘛
What are you doing?
保护戴恩
Keep Dane safe!
瑟希 等等 什么
Sersi, wait! What?
你没事
You're fine, dude.
丝派克
Sprite!
不行 爬楼梯
No. Stairs.
快跑 快…
Run! Go! Go!
快　-快点
- Go! - Come on!
它知道我们在哪
It knows where we are!
怎么会
How?
我不知道
I don't know!
丝派克
Sprite!
伊卡利斯
Ikaris!
晚安 两位小姐
Evening, ladies.
小心
Watch out!
巫师
Wizard.
我以为死定了
对不起
Sorry.
它自愈了吗
Did it just heal itself?
伊卡利斯
Ikaris.
好高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
我也很高兴见到你 丝派克
It's good to see you, too, Sprite.
我是戴恩
I'm Dane.
你好 戴恩
Hello, Dane.
我猜你就是那个飞行员
Well, I guess you must be the pilot.
我们是永恒族 来自奥林匹亚星
We're Eternals, from a planet called Olympia.
七千年前搭多摩号星舰前来
We came here 7,000 years ago on the Domo,
保护人类免于变异族侵害
our starship, to protect humans from the Deviants.
我们以为在五世纪前杀光了它们
We thought we killed them all five centuries ago,
如今它们又回来了
but now they're back.
如果你不想搬来跟我住 可以直说
Look, if you don't want to move in with me, you could just say.
戴恩 我是认真的
Dane, this is serious.
我知道 我还不能接受你不是巫师
Oh, I know. I'm just still getting over the fact you're not a wizard.
本来希望你能把我变成长颈鹿
I was hoping you could change me into a giraffe.
小时候我想当长颈鹿
I always wanted to be a giraffe when I was a kid.
可惜我不能改变有感情的动物
It's too bad I can't change sentient beings.
你会是很可爱的长颈鹿
You would have made a very cute giraffe.
你们怎么不帮忙对抗萨诺斯
Why didn't you guys help fight Thanos?
阻止战争 或史上其他可怕的事
Or any war? Or all the other terrible things throughout history?
我们接获指示 不能介入人类冲突
We were instructed not to interfere in any human conflicts
除非有变异族出现
unless Deviants were involved.
为什么
Why?
如果七千年来我们一直保护人类
If we'd protected humanity from everything for 7,000 years,
你们永远没机会以自己的方式发展
you'd never have had the chance to develop in the way you were meant to.
如果变异族很久以前就消灭了
But if the Deviants were eradicated a long time ago,
你们为何还在这里
why are you still here?
我们一直在等待
We've been waiting...
可以回家的通知
to be told we can go home.
所以…
So...
伊卡利斯
Ikaris.
飞得离太阳太近的男孩
The boy who flew too close to the sun.
我们住雅典时 丝派克编了这故事
Sprite made that story up when we lived in Athens.
公元前5世纪
In the fifth century BC?
你们俩在一起多久了
How long were you two together?
五千年
5,000 years.
那算长期交往了
I guess you can call that long-term.
发生了什么事
What happened?
他离开了
He left.
我一直以为他会回来 可是…
I always thought he'd come back, but...
从来没有
he never did.
所以我放下了
So, I moved on.
很高兴你放下了
I'm glad you did.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我该走了
I have to go.
今天早上 一场史无前例的全球地震
This morning, an unprecedented global earthquake
席卷世界各国
swept nation-states across the world,
造成损害和恐慌
causing damage and panic.
许多人猜测它与弹指事件有关
Many have speculated its connection with the Blip.
联合国呼吁召开紧急会议…
The UN has called for an emergency meeting...
那个变异族有办法自愈
That Deviant healed itself.
它们以前根本做不到
They could never do that before.
它不找人类却冲着我们来 怎么了
And it was coming after us instead of humans. What's going on?
我是因为地震才来看你们
I came to check on you because of the earthquake.
没听说过那个变异族
That Deviant is news to me.
地球出事了
Something's happening to Earth.
这不可能是巧合
Can't be a coincidence.
我们需要找到其他族人
We need to find the others.
有些人几百年没见了
I haven't seen some of them for centuries.
应该没多大变化
I doubt much has changed.
抱歉我伤害了你 瑟希
I'm sorry I hurt you, Sersi.
但我们需要团结
But we need to stick together.
只要确定你安全 我就不烦你
And once I know you're safe, I'll leave you alone.
我们先去找艾贾克
Let's go to Ajak first.
她知道该怎么做
She'll know what to do.
听到了吗 丝派克
You hear that, Sprite?
家人团圆
Family reunion.
也该是时候了
It's about time.
那个是我的 算了
Hey, that one was mine! Oh, never mind.
不要害怕
Do not fear.
快到大门里面
Quickly, inside the gate!
（公元前575年 巴比伦）
艾贾克
Ajak.
阿里瑟姆
Arishem.
我们继续保护巴比伦不受变异族侵害
We continue to keep Babylon safe from the Deviants.
越来越多的人前来寻求庇护
More people have come to seek refuge.
它现在是地球上最大的城市
It is now the largest city on Earth.
在各银河系执行任务的永恒族
The Eternals serving their missions across the galaxies
将以你们的成功为榜样
will learn from your success.
谢谢
Thank you.
我尊重你的宏伟计划 阿里瑟姆
I respect your grand design, Arishem.
但我注意到这个星球的特别之处
But I have noticed something special about this planet.
我担心或许这一次的代价…
And I fear that maybe this time the cost may...
不要对这个星球动感情
Do not become attached to this planet.
你必须专注于任务真正的使命
You must focus on the true purpose of your mission.
我明白
I understand.
我不会让你失望
I will not let you down.
费斯托斯
Phastos.
昨晚有没有听我的话去跑趴
Did you go to the party last night like I told you to?
跑趴 有
The party, yeah.
他熬夜工作
- Yeah, it was... - He worked all night.
谁在跟你说话
Who was talking to you?
要有自己的生活 瑟希呢
Get a life. And where is Sersi?
照常迟到
Late as usual.
抱歉 我有令人兴奋的东西给你看
I'm sorry, but I have something very exciting to show you, okay?
等著瞧
Wait till you see this.
它是什么
What is it?
一具引擎
It's an engine.
它将蒸汽从高压转移到低压
It moves steam from high pressure to low pressure.
帮助他们以超高速耕田
Uh, it'll help them till their fields at an incredibly fast rate.
会吓坏他们
It's gonna freak them out.
他们发明轮子才一千年
I mean, they only have had the wheel 1,000 years, so...
我们可以用你的意念控制他们
You know, we could do that thing where you use your mind to control them
他们就能进步得更快
and then they could do it quicker.
艾贾克 你有在听吗
Ajak, you listening to this?
费斯托斯 这蒸汽…
Phastos, this steam...
引擎 是蒸汽引擎　-太早了
Engine. It's a steam engine. It's too soon.
她来了
And there she is.
我错过什么
What did I miss?
没什么 只有我大失所望的尖叫声
Nothing. Just the screams of my deep disappointment.
我相信你有更简单的东西
I am sure you have something simpler.
简单
Simple.
好吧 我看看
Okay, let's see. Uh...
各位先生女士 向你们介绍
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you
犁
the plow.
那就是它的功用
'Cause that's what it does.
犁土
Plows dirt.
我遇到一群移居者在北部田野盖住家
I met another group of settlers who are building their homes in the northern fields.
他们会需要种自己的作物
They'll need to plant their own crops.
谢谢你 瑟希　-听我说
- Thanks, Sersi. - Listen,
人类比我们有些人希望的发展更慢
humanity may be coming along slower than some of us want.
或许他们在进步过程中会发现奇迹
But there is no telling what wonders they will discover as they advance.
世界的奇迹等着你
The wonders of the world await you.
跟随吉尔伽美什与恩奇都加入战争
Follow Gilgamesh and Enkidu into battle.
永远受他们的勇敢和力量所鼓舞
Be forever inspired by their bravery and strength.
你和你的同胞…
You and your fellow man...
将踏上伟大的冒险之旅
...will go on great adventures.
成为你们自己的传奇
And become legends of your own!
我看到了
I just saw that.
明明还有很多椅子
There's so many other chairs, man.
我能用我的能力…
You know, I could use my powers...
过来陪我喝一杯
Come and have a drink with me.
不了
No.
我不能让你独自对抗变异族
I can't let you go and fight Deviants on your own.
我们需要守护这座城市　-让开
We need to guard the city. Get out of my way.
我来这个星球不是为了缩在墙后
I didn't come to this planet to cower behind walls.
我们得相信阿里瑟姆对这星球的安排
We need to trust Arishem's design for this planet.
圣娜
Thena.
与你并肩作战是我的荣幸
It's an honor to fight alongside you.
我也一样
And you.
美丽的玛卡瑞 你迟到了
My beautiful Makkari. You're late.
我要有足够的工艺品才能换到好东西
I needed to get enough artifacts to make a good trade.
骗她就好了
Just lie to her.
我能感觉到振动
I can sense vibrations. I can sense vibrations.
即使是最微小的动作
Even the tiniest movement.
包括你们说话的声音
Including your voices when you speak.
你们俩在浪费我的时间吗
Did you two just waste my time?
你正在寻找的《翠玉录》
The Emerald Tablet you're searching for...
是个谜
...is a myth!
当人类发生冲突时
When humans have conflict,
艾贾克告诉我们不要干涉
Ajak tells us not to interfere.
她还说偷窃非常非常糟糕
Well, she also says that stealing is very, very bad.
如果你不说
If you don't tell,
我也不会说
I won't tell.
一言为定
Deal.
我保证不让我对瑟希的感情影响任务
I promise I won't let my feelings for Sersi distract me from my mission.
人类无力保护自己免受变异族侵害
Humans are far from being able to protect themselves from the Deviants.
我们还有很多事要做
We still have much to do.
你对阿里瑟姆的信心很坚定
Your faith in Arishem is strong.
我感觉得到
I can feel it.
但你也能过自己的生活 知道吗
But you are allowed to live a life, you know?
告诉瑟希你的感受
Go tell Sersi how you feel.
试试看
Try.
对不起 我搞砸了
Sorry. I'm making a mess.
嗯 还不错
Well, not bad.
再见
See you.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
它和你的眼睛很搭
It matches your eyes.
你真好心
You are very kind.
你在学他们的语言了
You're learning their language now?
如果我想花更多时间陪你
If I want to spend more time with you,
就需要了解他们
I need to get to know them.
我非常漂亮
I am very beautiful.
等等 我说了什么
Wait, what did I say?
你说「我非常漂亮」
You said, "I am very beautiful."
你…
You...
你非常漂亮 瑟希
You are very beautiful, Sersi.
我是你的 瑟希
I'm yours, Sersi,
只要你愿意接受我
if you'll have me.
我爱你 伊卡利斯
I love you, Ikaris.
我爱你 瑟希
I love you, Sersi.
（公元400年 笈多帝国）
愿诸神在此见证你们结为连理
May the gods hereby bond you in matrimony.
恭喜
Congratulations.
（今日 南达科他州）
有人在吗
Hello?
艾贾克
Ajak?
Ajak!
是变异族干的
It was a Deviant.
我们的爱
Our love
还有我们的忠诚
And our devotion
如海洋一样深
Were as deep as any ocean
那是我最后一次见到她
It was the last time I saw her.
艾贾克请我看看瑟希 所以我去伦敦
Ajak asked me to check on Sersi, so I went to London.
原来我们俩都很寂寞 需要彼此
Turned out, both of us were lonely and we needed each other.
我想艾贾克一直…
I guess, in her way,
用她的方式照顾着我们
Ajak never stopped trying to take care of us.
再见 艾贾克
Bye, Ajak.
这是我们七千年来第一次有人死亡
It's the first time in 7,000 years one of us has died.
我想在伦敦攻击我们的那个变异族
I think the Deviant that attacked us in London
杀死了艾贾克 并吸取她的力量
killed Ajak and absorbed her power.
变异族从未这么做过
Deviants have never done that in the past.
它就像艾贾克一样自愈
It healed itself just like Ajak.
我发誓 我几乎听到它说话
I swear, I almost heard it speak.
阿里瑟姆
- Arishem.
瑟希
- Sersi.
时间差不多了
It is almost time.
瑟希…你还好吗
Sersi! Sersi! Are you okay?
怎么了 瑟希
What happened, Sersi?
艾贾克用来和阿里瑟姆交谈的球
The sphere that Ajak used to talk with Arishem,
从她的身体飘出来 进入我体内
it came out of her body and went inside me.
你和阿里瑟姆谈过
Did you talk with Arishem?
对 他说…
Yes. He said
时间差不多了
it's almost time.
你能设法再跟他说话吗
Can you try talking to him again?
我不知道怎么做
I don't know how.
但她选择了你来接替她
But she chose you to replace her.
她给了你那颗球
And she gave you the sphere.
等等 丝派克
Hold on, Sprite.
你确定你和阿里瑟姆谈过
Are you sure you talked with Arishem?
不然会是什么
What else would it be?
永魔症
Mahd Wy'ry.
（1521年 特诺奇蒂特兰）
其他人在哪里
Where are the others?
我们不得不分开
We had to split up.
变异族比你说的还多
There were more Deviants than you said.
相信你们玩得很尽兴
Well, I'm sure that was a lot of fun for you.
没错
It was.
等其他人杀死最后的变异族
Once the others kill these last Deviants,
就把它们从这星球上彻底歼灭了
we will have eliminated them all from the planet.
不要
Don't.
我们不干涉他们的战争
We don't interfere in their wars.
这不是战争
This isn't war.
是种族灭绝
It's genocide.
他们的武器变得太致命了
Their weapons have become too deadly.
帮他们进步并非好主意 费斯托斯
Maybe it wasn't such a good idea helping them advance, Phastos.
科技是他们演化过程的一部分 诸克
Technology is a part of their evolutionary process, Druig.
那不是我能阻止的
It's not exactly something that I can stop.
对 你不能 但我可以
No, you can't. But I can.
坚强点
Stay strong.
太迟了
It's too late.
圣娜 　-每个人都会死
Thena? Everyone is going to die.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
圣娜
Thena?
圣娜…不　-圣娜
Thena? Thena, no! Thena!
不要听你脑中的指示 圣娜
Don't listen to your head, Thena.
听我的声音
Listen to my voice.
你很安全
You are safe.
你感受到爱
You are loved.
你是我们的圣娜
You're our Thena.
圣娜
Hey, Thena!
住手…
Hey! Stop, stop, stop!
她还好吗 　-嗯
- Is she okay? - Yeah.
瑟希
Sersi.
圣娜 求求你
Thena, please.
回到我们身边
Come back to us.
好
Okay.
我以为永魔症是没根据的说法
I thought Mahd Wy'ry was a myth.
无药可救
There is no cure...
所以没人真的去谈它
so no one really talks about it.
发生了什么事
What happened?
圣娜
Thena.
你攻击所有人
You attacked everyone.
你打伤瑟希、费斯托斯
Wounded Sersi, Phastos,
差点杀死玛卡瑞
you nearly killed Makkari.
我不记得了
I don't remember.
你得了永魔症
You have Mahd Wy'ry.
你的意念因记忆的重压逐渐瓦解
Your mind is fracturing under the weight of your memories.
我只能清除它们 让你重新开始
And all I can do is erase them so that you can start over.
我必须通知阿里瑟姆 带你回舰上
I will have to inform Arishem and take you back to the ship
那里有科技能帮你
where we have the technology to help you.
但她就不再是圣娜了
But she won't be Thena anymore.
如果再发生呢 她差点杀了你
What if it happens again? She could've killed you.
差点杀了我们所有人
She could have killed all of us.
拜托
Please.
拜托 我想记住
Please, I... I want to remember.
我想记住我的人生
I want to remember my life.
圣娜 我爱你
Thena, I love you.
可是听我说
But listen to me.
你记不记得并不重要
It's not important if you remember or not.
你的精神会留存下来
Your spirit will remain.
内心深处永远都是圣娜
You will always be Thena deep inside.
相信我
Trust me.
她凭什么相信你
Why should she trust you?
你要她让你清除她的身份
You're asking her to let you erase who she is.
诸克 我知道你很不满 但是…
Druig, I know you're upset, but...
不满
Upset?
我们相信你七千年 看看我们的处境
We've trusted you for 7,000 years, and look where you've gotten us.
我目睹人类互相残杀
I've watched humans destroy each other
而我明明能出手阻止
when I could stop it all in a heartbeat.
知道千百年后这对一个人的影响吗
Do you know what that does to someone after centuries?
我们的任务会不会是一个错误
Could our mission have been a mistake?
我们真在帮这些人建立更好的世界
Are we really helping these people build a better world, huh?
我们跟底下的士兵没两样
We're just like the soldiers down there.
不过是他们领袖的棋子
Pawns to their leaders.
被忠诚所蒙蔽
Blinded by loyalty.
现在结束了
It ends now.
放了他们
Let them go.
你得逼我才行
You're gonna have to make me.
住手
Stop.
如果你想阻止我
If you wanna stop me,
就得杀了我
you're gonna have to kill me.
我会照顾圣娜
I'll watch over Thena.
让她保留她的记忆
Let her keep her memories.
有一天当她攻击你
One day, when she attacks you,
你可能必须杀了她
you might have to kill her.
我们愿意冒险
We'll take that chance.
你们都可以走了
You may all go.
变异族消失了
The Deviants are gone.
你们没必要待在我身边
There is no reason for you to stay with me.
你不该先问问阿里瑟姆吗
Shouldn't you ask Arishem first?
我们是一个团队 应该待在一起
We're a team, we should stay together.
我没有问你的意见 伊卡利斯
I didn't ask you for your advice, Ikaris.
不要忘记你的身份
Do not forget your place.
我们就在这里道别吧
This is where we say goodbye.
你们可以走了
You are free to go.
我要你们出去
I want you to go out there.
为自己而活
And live a life for yourselves.
不是以军人的身份
Not as soldiers.
不是为了原本的使命
Not with the purpose you were given.
去寻找自己的目标
Find your own purpose.
有一天 当我们再次聚首
And one day, when we see each other again,
我要你们告诉我找到了什么
I want you to tell me what you found.
过来吧
Come my way Nach, mera hero
（今日 孟买）
赶走邪恶
Get the evil away
你前来拯救
You came to save
如今你在这里
And now you're here
现在你回家了 全都给我
Now you have come home Give it all to me
你会为了我的胜利不顾一切
You would risk it all For the victory
我几乎不能等待你
Waiting for you Scarcely can I
欢迎
Welcome.
我是卡伦帕特尔
I am Karun Patel.
金勾的贴身助理
Kingo's valet.
十分荣幸见到伟大的永恒族
It's truly an honor to be in the presence of the great Eternals.
火环宛如太阳
Like the fire Like the sun
你已变得强大
You have risen, Mighty one
卡 各位 非常好
Cut! Okay, everyone, that was good.
但可以再好上10%
But we could do 10% better.
太棒了 非常非常好
That was beautiful. Very, very good.
真的太棒了
Really, so good.
我的大学同学来了
My friends from college are here.
你好 老大
Hello, boss!
来得正好 欢迎光临拍摄片场
Perfect timing! Welcome to the set of...
《伊卡利斯传奇》
Legend of Ikaris.
我饰演你
I'm playing you!
喜欢这套服装吗 　-我们需要谈谈
You like the costume? We need to talk.
跟导演说我有笔记要给他
Tell the director I have some notes for him...
我们需要和你私下谈
We need to talk to you in private.
卡伦跟着我50年了 我十分信任他
Oh, Karun, he's worked with me for 50 years. I trust him completely.
第一次见面时 他以为我是吸血鬼
Actually, when we first met, he thought I was a vampire,
试图刺穿我的心脏
and he tried to stake me through the heart.
我已经道歉很多次了
I have apologized so many times.
次数不够 但很接近 我再告诉你
Not quite enough times. Very close, though. I'll let you know.
我得准备拍下一场 到我的帐篷谈
Oh, I have to get ready for the next scene. Come to my tent, we'll talk there.
你们会爱死下一场
You guys are gonna love the next scene.
我得吊钢丝 毕竟我不会飞
I come in on a wire 'cause, you know, I can't fly.
等等 我们要再合体了吗
Wait, are we getting back together?
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
我一直在等
I've been waiting for the day
世人得知影子战士的真实身份
the world learns the true identity of the Shadow Warrior.
艾贾克死了
Ajak's dead.
她遭人杀害
She was killed.
是变异族干的
It was a Deviant.
变异族回来了
The Deviants are back.
我们不知道有多少个
We don't know how many there are.
你必须跟我们走
You need to come with us.
（《影子战士3》）
我不能就这样走 这些人都依赖我
I can't just go. I mean, all these people depend on me.
这部片刚开拍 是三部曲的第一部
We just started shooting this movie. It's the first of a trilogy.
我们找了防弹少年团客串
We just got BTS to do a cameo...
先生
Sir,
我能说句话吗 　-什么都别说
may I say something? Please don't say anything.
我认为你应该去
I think you should go.
我说什么都不要说
I just said don't say anything.
「人生最大的责任莫过于保护家人」
"Life affords no greater duty than to protect one's family!"
记得吗 你最喜欢的台词
Remember? It's your favorite line
出自《影子战士2：时光之旅》
from The Shadow Warrior 2: Voyage of Time.
你家人需要你
Your family needs you.
七千年
Seven thousand years.
永恒族和变异族交战了这么久
That's how long the battle between Eternals and Deviants has raged for.
你以为我是电影明星
You think I'm a movie star.
我是 但我也是…
Well, I am. But I am also...
永恒族
an Eternal.
金勾 你在做什么
Kingo, what are you doing?
人们应该记住我们 所以…
I think we should be remembered, so...
我在拍一部关于我们的纪录片
I am making a documentary about us.
你将见到我的永恒族同胞 丝派克
You are about to meet my fellow Eternal, Sprite.
丝派克 自我介绍一下
Sprite, tell them about yourself.
等一下
Oh, wait.
好吧 等等再拍她
Okay, well, we'll circle back to her.
这是瑟希
This is Sersi.
瑟希
Sersi,
向大家自我介绍
tell them about yourself.
我们在拍了
We're rolling.
好
Well, uh...
我能把石头变成水
I can change a rock into water.
我能把石头变成木头
Uh, I could turn a rock into wood.
或把石头变成金属
Or a rock into metal.
有一次我还把石头变成空气
Actually, one time, I turned a rock into air.
卡
Cut.
这样吧 你想一下 等等回来拍你
Um, you know what? Why don't you think about it, and we'll get back to you, okay?
我们走
Let's go.
丝派克说你迷上了那玩意
Sprite says you're addicted to this thing.
这个
Oh, this?
你看
Look at this.
毕竟我们不会老
You know, seeing as we don't age.
你看上去挺帅的
I think you look quite good.
对不对
Don't you?
没人想过你为何当男主角一百多年
Nobody ever wonders how you managed to be the leading man for over 100 years?
我不知道你在说什么
Oh, I don't know what you're talking about.
那是我的曾曾祖父
That is my great-great-grandfather,
那是我曾祖父
that is my great-grandfather,
祖父
grandfather,
父亲 还有我
father, and me.
我是宝莱坞史上最伟大王朝的一员
I'm part of the greatest dynasty in the history of Bollywood.
了不起吧
Pretty impressive, right?
你在马其顿抛弃我
You abandoned me in Macedonia.
好啦 我厌倦了每五年搬一次家
Okay, I got sick of moving every five years.
人们注意到你不会老就…
People freak out when they notice that you don't...
抓狂
age.
我以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
知道我为什么热爱电影吗
Do you know why I love movies?
因为你
Because of you.
我想念坐在观众席上 听你的故事
I missed sitting in the audience, listening to your stories,
看着你的幻象
watching your illusions.
我们应该聚在一起才对
We should've all stayed together.
那艾贾克就会还活着
Ajak would still be alive.
她根本不该让我们走
She should have never let us go.
（澳大利亚）
这是你在伦敦打过的变异族
This is the Deviant you fought in London?
不一样
It's different.
数量一定比我们想的多
There must be more out there than we thought.
这是变异族吗 先生
Is... Is this a Deviant, sir?
是
Yep.
好美的生物
It's a beautiful creature.
什么 这个 不 很丑恶
What? This? This? No. It's hideous.
你没碰过想咬掉你的头的 开始拍
You've never had one try to bite your head off. Roll.
你即将见到史上最伟大的两名战士
You're about to meet two of the greatest warriors the world has ever known.
圣娜 传奇、致命、时尚
Thena, legendary, deadly, fashionable.
还有她值得信赖的朋友
And her trusty friend...
拍门
Door.
力大无穷
...a mighty powerhouse of strength,
令人丧胆的吉尔伽美什
the fearsome Gilgamesh!
吉尔伽美什
Gilgamesh!
（亲吻厨师）
你们怎么拖这么久
What took you so long?
你今天看上去比较年轻 丝派克
You look younger today, Sprite.
我有同样的围裙
I have the same apron.
你哪位
Who the hell are you?
我是卡伦 金勾的贴身助理
I'm Karun. Kingo's valet.
贴身助理 就像《蝙蝠侠》里的阿福
Oh, valet. Like Alfred in Batman.
吉尔伽美什 变异族回来了
Gilgamesh. The Deviants are back.
是哦 我是需要帮手
No shit. I could have used some help.
我们在伦敦也遭到一个变异族攻击
We were attacked by a Deviant in London, too.
就连伊卡利斯也杀不死它
Even Ikaris couldn't kill it.
你不能
You couldn't?
我心有旁骛
I was distracted.
当然
Sure, man.
你们想尝尝我的派吗
Hey, you guys wanna try my pie?
很遗憾 吉尔
I'm sorry, Gil.
艾贾克死了
Ajak's dead.
真的 老哥
It's true, buddy.
我们失去她了
We lost her.
瑟希
Sersi.
那次攻击触动了她的情绪
The attack triggered her.
现在接近她得小心
She's no fun to be around right now.
圣娜
Hey, Thena.
你看谁来了
Look who's here.
把你的手给我
Give me your hand.
圣娜
Thena.
仙图里六的每个人都会死
Everyone in Centuri-6 is going to die.
把你的手给我
Give me your hand.
太迟了 我们救不了他们
It's too late. We can't save them.
圣娜
Thena.
我们一起搭星舰来到地球
We came to Earth together on our ship.
你是永恒族
You're an Eternal.
奥林匹亚星最伟大的战士
The greatest warrior of Olympia.
传奇的雅典保护者
The legendary protector of Athens.
女战神
The goddess of war.
记住你的身份
Remember who you are.
记住
Remember.
圣娜　-你好
Thena. Hi.
哈啰
Hello.
你的园丁是谁
Hey, who's your gardener?
这就是你们每天吃的东西
This is just what you guys eat every day?
对 太棒了　-每天
Yeah, this is amazing. Every day.
谢谢你的招待　-不客气
Thank you for this. Oh, you're welcome.
自己动手
Help yourself.
这是葡萄酒、啤酒和蜂蜜酒混成的
This one is a trio of wine, beer, and mead.
为特洛伊战争的士兵调制的
Made for all the soldiers in the battle of Troy.
真是太周到了
That's so thoughtful.
她该喝酒吗
Should she be drinking?
不 她的不含酒精 小孩喝的
No, hers is non-alcoholic. For kids.
我给了你一样的 丝派克
I gave you the same thing, Sprite.
小孩喝的
For kids.
我开玩笑的
I was just kidding.
你喝的是奥丁教我的密酿
Yours is a secret brew Odin taught me as a thank-you
感谢我们在滕斯贝格击败劳菲的军队
after we helped defeat Laufey's army in Tonsberg.
什么
What?
（吉尔伽美湿）
我是个大宝宝
I'm a big baby.
真不幼稚 可以停了吗
Very mature. Can you stop?
别闹了　-说到奥丁
- Stop. - Speaking of Odin...
索尔小时候常跟在我屁股后面
Thor used to follow me around when he was a little kid.
现在他是知名的复仇者 不回我电话
Now he's a famous Avenger and won't return my calls.
既然罗杰斯队长和钢铁人都走了
So, now that Captain Rogers and Iron Man are both gone,
你想谁能带领复仇者联盟
who do you think is gonna lead the Avengers?
我可以带领他们
I could lead them.
我认为我会很出色
I figure I'd be good at that.
对 你会
Yeah, you would.
艾贾克竟然没选你来领导我们
Ajak didn't even choose you to lead us.
吉尔 唉唷
Ouch, Gil. Ouch.
好狠哦　-我当你没说
Harsh. I'm gonna let that one slide
你一向受不了我能飞 而你不能
because, you know, you've always been bitter that I can fly and you can't.
你能飞又怎样
Oh, so what, you can fly.
大家都知道我长得比较好看
I'm better-looking, everybody knows that.
你去哪
Where you going?
出去透透气
I'm just gonna get some air.
真的很好喝 吉尔
Mmm. This is really good, Gil.
我能拿来卖 把我的脸放上面当卖点
You know, I could sell this. Put my face on it, move some units.
我用玉米做的
I made it from corn.
我亲自咀嚼玉米粒 再用口水发酵
I chew each kernel myself and ferment it in my spit.
这就是圣娜说的仙图里六吗
Is this the Centuri-6 Thena was talking about?
对 它是一颗星球
Yeah, it's a planet.
她认为她住过那里 直到它被摧毁
She thinks she used to live there until it was destroyed.
常谈到瓦解它的那些超大震动
Always talks about massive quakes ripping it apart.
每个人都死了 包括她自己
Everyone died, including herself.
三天前发生了史无前例的全球大地震
We had an unprecedented global earthquake three days ago.
原来如此
Oh, that's what that was.
我以为我喝醉了
I thought I was drunk.
艾贾克选择我来领导我们 但是…
Ajak chose me to lead us, but...
我根本不懂如何和阿里瑟姆对谈
I can't even figure out how to speak to Arishem.
我试过好多次
I've tried so many times.
也许你试得太用力了
Maybe you're trying too hard.
有时你只需要倾听
Sometimes, you just have to listen.
瑟希
Sersi.
阿里瑟姆
Arishem.
艾贾克被一个变异族杀害
Ajak was killed by a Deviant.
我们认为它吸取了她的力量
We think it absorbed her power.
地球发生了一件不寻常的事
And something unusual is happening to Earth.
这是神现的副作用
It is a side effect of the emergence.
神现
The emergence?
是该让你了解任务的真正目的了
It is time for you to learn the true purpose of your mission.
你们被派到地球是为催生天神蒂亚穆
You were sent to Earth to bring forth the Celestial Tiamut.
每十亿年 新的天神族必须诞生
Every billion years, new Celestials must be born.
我将天神族种子
I plant Celestial seeds into host planets
散播于宇宙各创决星球
across the universe.
地球被选来创决天神蒂亚穆
The planet Earth was chosen to host the Celestial Tiamut.
为了成长
In order to grow,
蒂亚穆需要大量来自智慧生命的能量
Tiamut needs vast amounts of energy from intelligent life.
变异族食用人类 阻碍了这一点
The Deviants prevented this by consuming humans
直到永恒族消灭它们
until the Eternals eliminated them.
如今这个星球的人口已达到所需数量
Now, the human population of this planet has reached the required amount.
该是神现开始的时候了
It is time for the emergence to begin.
可是…
But...
地球上的每个人都会死
everyone on Earth will die.
瑟希 一个生命的终结
The end of one life, Sersi,
是另一个生命的开端
is the beginning of another.
我们的宇宙就是不断的能量交换
Our universe is a constant exchange of energy.
创造与毁灭的无限循环
An infinite cycle of creation and destruction.
天神族运用
Celestials use energy
创决星球聚集的能量来创造太阳
gathered from host planets to create suns,
产生重力、热和光
generating gravity, heat, and light
以形成新的银河系
for new galaxies to form.
没有我们
Without us,
我们的宇宙将陷入黑暗
our universe will fall into darkness.
所有生命都会死去
All life will die.
艾贾克知道真相吗
Ajak knew the truth?
数百万年来 她协助许多天神族出现
She has helped many Celestials to emerge over millions of years.
你也是
So have you.
但地球是我的第一次任务
Earth was my first mission.
我原本在家乡 奥林匹亚星
I was home, on Olympia.
根本没有奥林匹亚星
There is no Olympia.
这才是你真正的家乡 瑟希
This is your true home, Sersi.
世界熔炉
The World Forge.
我在这里创造并设计了永恒族
It is here that I built and programmed the Eternals.
除了我们 一切都会死去
Everything dies except us
因为我们从未活过
because we were never alive.
我怎么一点都不记得
Why don't I remember any of this?
你的记忆在每次神现后会清除与重置
Because your memories are erased and reset after each emergence.
它们储存在这里
They are stored here.
你为何保留它们
Why do you keep them?
我保留它们是为了研究变异族
I keep them in order to study the Deviants.
我创造了变异族 瑟希
I created the Deviants, Sersi,
目的跟我创造你们是一样的
for the same purpose I created you.
每个天神族创决星球有自己的掠食者
Every Celestial host planet has its own predators.
我最初派变异族去消灭它们
I first sent the Deviants to exterminate them
好让智慧生命可以生长
so intelligent life could grow.
但它们的设计里出现瑕疵
But there was a flaw in their design.
它们逐渐演化
They evolved.
自己变成掠食者
Became predators themselves.
我失去了对它们的控制力
And I lost control of them.
我创造并设计你们 永恒族
I built and programmed you, Eternals,
成为无法演化的合成体
to be synthetic beings and incapable of evolution,
以纠正我的错误
to correct my mistake.
瑟希 艾贾克选择你来接替她
Sersi, Ajak has chosen you to take her place
担任永恒族至尊
as the Prime Eternal.
不要让我失望
Do not fail me.
你是说我们基本上是酷炫的机器人
So, you're saying we're basically fancy robots?
我们过去的记忆储存在太空中…
And our past memories are stored somewhere
某个地方
in space?
阿里瑟姆也创造了变异族
And Arishem made the Deviants.
对不起 圣娜
I'm sorry, Thena.
你曾试图警告我们
You tried to warn us.
上次阿里瑟姆重置你的记忆
The last time Arishem reset your memories,
一定出了差错
something must have gone wrong.
什么意思
What do you mean?
这不就是永魔症吗
Well, that's what Mahd Wy'ry is, isn't it?
圣娜始终记得我们被派往其他星球
All this time, Thena was remembering all the other planets we were sent to
每个人都在神现期间死去
and everyone dying during the emergence.
我以为我们是英雄
I thought we were heroes.
原来我们是坏人
Turns out we're the bad guys.
我们不是坏人 好吗
We're not the bad guys, okay?
我们帮助天神族在宇宙中扩展生命
We've helped the Celestials expand life across the universe.
这不是坏人的作为 好人才这么做
That's not what bad guys do. That's what good guys do.
每次无辜生命为更大的利益牺牲
Every time innocent lives have been sacrificed for the greater good,
结果都是错误
it turns out to be a mistake.
我们必须阻止神现
We have to stop the emergence.
瑟希 我们无权阻止天神族诞生
Sersi, we have no right to stop the birth of a Celestial.
一定能让蒂亚穆出现又不摧毁地球
There has to be a way Tiamut can emerge without destroying the Earth.
我们只要让它延后 直到想出办法
We just have to delay it until we figure out how.
诸克能控制它的意念吗
Could Druig control its mind?
也许让它睡着
Maybe put it to sleep?
让它睡着
"Put it to sleep"?
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
吉尔伽美什曾要诸克让我睡着
Gilgamesh asked Druig to put me to sleep once.
所以我能到斐济度假
So I could take a vacation to Fiji, you know?
我们在讲天神族　-我们必须试试
We're talking about a Celestial, okay? We have to try.
我们不会让地球上所有人死掉吧
Come on, we're not gonna let everyone on Earth die, right?
对
Right.
我是人类 我有点偏心
I'm human. I'm a little biased.
世界末日快来了
The world is ending.
你得回家去
You need to go home.
做什么
And do what?
看电视吗
Watch TV?
在我能和地球最初的超级英雄
When I could be with the Earth's original superheroes
一起拯救世界时
as they try to save the world?
好
Fine.
如果你想 就留下
If you want to, stay.
非常谢谢你 先生
Thank you very much, sir.
吉尔伽美什
Gilgamesh,
能请你拿走口水啤酒吗
could you please get rid of the saliva beer?
我以为你喜欢
I thought you like it, man.
我们该走了 现在
We need to go. Now.
去找其他人
Find the others.
一旦我们聚在一起
Once we're all together,
就能决定如何处理神现
we'll decide what to do about the emergence.
（亚马逊雨林）
午安
Good afternoon.
这里感觉真好 先生
It's very nice here, sir.
不要被耍了
Don't be fooled.
无知就是福
Ignorance is bliss.
嗨 我们在找诸克
Hey. We're looking for Druig.
他在这里吗
Is he here?
在
Yes.
你怎么认识诸克
How do you know Druig?
我们是朋友
We're friends...
大学认识的
...from college.
你好 丝派克
Hello, Sprite.
我想念你们大家
I missed all of you.
请 就当自己家
Please, make yourselves at home.
你一口气给了我很多坏消息 小姐
You've given me a lot of bad news in one go, my lady.
你愿意帮我们吗
Will you help us?
我很高兴…
I am glad that...
（戴恩惠特曼）
你用哪家电信
Hey, what's your service?
我没讯号
I'm not getting any bars.
还记得这片森林吗 好美
Do you all remember this forest? Beautiful.
我们同住的最后一个地方
It was the last place we all lived together.
我保护这些人20代了
I've protected these people for 20 generations now
不受外界和他们自己侵害
from the outside world and from themselves.
朋友 人类未来要为自己的灭绝负责
Your kind, my friend, you will be responsible for your own extinction one day.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
我们必须从错误中学习 做得更好
I think we must learn from our mistakes and do better, sir.
你不能放弃希望
You must not give up hope.
不会吧
Oh, no, you didn't.
新规定 不能再附身别人的助理
Okay, new rule, no more possessing people's valets.
你的幽默感哪去了 金勾
Oh, where is your sense of humor, Kingo?
对不起 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
不要道歉 不是你的错
Don't apologize, it's not your fault.
你不是神 你知道吧
You are not a god. You know that, right?
真讽刺 金勾 电影明星
How ironic. Kingo, the movie star.
我也导过几部片
I've directed some things, too.
是吗 像什么
Oh, yeah? Like what?
一些网络视频
Some Internet content.
多少次点阅
How many views?
我不是为了点阅数拍的
I don't do it for the views.
走吧 他在浪费我们时间
Let's go. He's wasting our time.
我们需要他　-伊卡利斯
- We need him. - Ikaris.
我很想你
I missed you.
你是要迷惑我还是威胁我
Are you gonna charm me or threaten me?
如果你愿意 有第三种选择
I mean, there's a third option, if you prefer that.
发现你不是妈妈的最爱 一定很难过
It must be heartbreaking to find out that you're not Mother's favorite.
她一定为你所做的感到骄傲
And I'm sure she'd be real proud of what you've been up to.
诸克 这件事很严重
Druig, this is serious.
我告诉你什么叫严重
I'll tell you what's serious.
原来七千年来我都在执行自杀任务
I've just been told I've been sent on a suicide mission for the past 7,000 years,
我的存在是一则谎言
and that my entire existence is a lie.
所以原谅我现在不想鸟你的计划
So, excuse me for not giving a shit about your plan right now.
诸克烂透了
Druig sucks.
真的 先生
He does, sir.
我不喜欢这个地方
I don't like this place.
诸克需要思考 瑟希要我们等
Druig needs to think, and Sersi wants us to wait, so...
我们只好等
we wait.
我在丝派克的幻象中认不出自己
I couldn't recognize myself in Sprite's illusions.
那是美好的往日时光
Those were the good old days.
如果我再也无法战斗了呢
What if I can't fight anymore?
你当然可以
Of course you can. Mm.
要是我又伤害你们呢
What if I hurt you again?
你知道自己是谁 你是女战神圣娜
Come on. You know who you are. You're Thena, goddess of war.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢什么
For what?
一直照顾我
For always taking care of me. Oh.
我会再做一次
I'd do it again.
在任何星球上
On any planet.
我也喜欢死盯着他
I like watching him, too.
天啊
Jeez.
我觉得一点也不诡异
I don't think it's creepy at all.
你读过《彼得潘》吗
Have you read Peter Pan?
对我来说 伊卡利斯就是彼得
Okay, so, to me, Ikaris is Peter,
瑟希是温蒂 你是奇妙仙子
Sersi is Wendy,
原因显而易见
you are Tinker Bell, for obvious reasons,
我们其他人则是走失的男孩
and the rest of us are the Lost Boys.
你想说什么
What's your point?
奇妙仙子一直爱着彼得
Tinker Bell's always been in love with Peter.
她很难受 因为她不可能和他在一起
And it's hard for her 'cause she can never be with him.
真遗憾 丝派克
I'm sorry, Sprite.
金勾
Kingo...
阿里瑟姆为何让我变这模样
why did Arishem make me this way?
我不知道
I don't know.
我以为你把它弄坏了
I thought you broke it.
我随身带备用机
Always bring backups.
先生 你家人很爱气噗噗
You have a very angry family, sir.
这是个大问题
Yeah, it's a big issue.
迈达斯王呢 他碰的东西都会变黄金
What about King Midas? Everything he touched turned to gold.
那是你吗 　-戴恩
Was that you? Dane.
孔子 亚里士多德 　-打给你叔叔
Confucius? Aristotle? Call your uncle.
什么 我叔叔 不
What? My uncle? No.
你一直想跟他和解吧
You've always wanted to make amends with him, right?
时候到了 相信我
Now is the time. Trust me.
瑟希 你好奇怪
Sersi, you're so weird.
戴恩 戴恩
Dane? Dane?
（讯号不良）
你断断续续的
You're breaking up.
你要跟他断了
You're breaking up?
他能接受吗
How did he take the news?
我无法告诉他世界末日到了
Couldn't bring myself to tell him it was the end of the world.
他也无能为力
There's nothing he could do.
瑟希
Sersi.
我很担心你
I'm worried about you.
如果阿里瑟姆发现你试图阻止神现
If Arishem finds out you're trying to stop the emergence...
我的力量不足以保护你不受他惩罚
I'm not powerful enough to protect you from him.
我不怕
I'm not afraid.
这个暴力循环必须划下句点
This violent cycle has to end.
别再担心我了
Hey, stop worrying about me.
习惯了
Old habit.
你为什么离开
Why did you leave?
我告诉自己
I told myself
你一定出了什么事
something must have happened to you.
所以我开始等
So, I waited.
好多天变成好多年
Days became years,
你始终没回来
and you never came back.
瑟希
Sersi,
我好想你
oh, I've missed you.
我也不想离开
I didn't want to leave.
有件事我必须…
There's something I have to tell...
伊卡利斯
Ikaris!
小姐
Miss?
你还好吗
You're ok?
小心
Watch out!
撤离营地
Clear the camp!
躲在我身后
Get behind me!
有一个带走伊卡利斯
One of them took Ikaris.
这是偷袭
It's an ambush!
好棒棒 先生
Very nice, sir!
你起肖了吗 躲起来
Are you mental? Hide!
我们需要动作场面
We need action sequences.
先生
Sir!
丝派克 带卡伦离开
Sprite, get Karun out of here.
年轻人 你带了几台摄像头
How many cameras did you bring, young man?
金勾
Kingo!
快走
Come on!
这边
This way!
快
Quickly! Come on!
进去…
Get in! Get in!
伊卡利斯
Ikaris!
我跟那个对打过 它比其他的强
I've fought that one before. It's stronger than the others.
不
No.
时机不对 圣娜
Terrible timing, Thena.
圣娜
Thena!
住手 圣娜
Stop, Thena!
放它们走
Let them go.
现在不是时候 瑟希
Now is not the time, Sersi.
拜托 我知道你没这么傻
Please. I know you're better than this.
诸克
Druig.
发生什么事
What's happening?
快走 去河边
Go! Get to the river!
吉尔伽美什
Gilgamesh.
能过来帮忙吗
A little help here?
留在这里
Stay here.
说
Say it.
留下
Stay here.
好 你没事
Good. You're okay.
它们往营地去了
They're headed for the camp.
走吧 他们需要你
Go. They need you.
快去 伊卡利斯
Go, Ikaris.
丝派克 帮我争取时间
Sprite, buy me some time!
你能快点吗
Can you hurry up?
好了
Now!
砰
Dishoom.
卡伦 你拍到了吗
Karun! Did you get that?
拍到了 先生
I did, sir!
金勾　-快走
Kingo! Just go.
我不会丢下你
I'm not leaving you.
丝派克
Sprite!
伊卡利斯
Ikaris!
瑟希 你没事吧
Sersi! Are you all right?
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
停…
Stop, stop, stop.
圣娜
Thena.
不 吉尔伽美什
No. Gilgamesh.
别过来
Stay back.
艾贾克
Ajak...
她的记忆
Her memories...
我现在懂了
I understand now.
我能看到她看到的
I can see what she saw.
好多星球
So many planets.
每当天神族诞生 就有好多生命殒落
So much life destroyed every time a Celestial is born.
阿里瑟姆利用我们
Arishem used us
每次神现就任我们死去
and left us to die with each emergence.
我们只想活下去
We just wanted to survive.
然后他派你们来
And then he sent you.
我会为你们对我族的恶行杀光你们
I will kill you all for what you have done to my kind.
你们不是救世主 永恒族
You are not saviors, Eternals.
你们是凶手
You are murderers.
伊卡利斯
Ikaris!
圣娜
Thena.
嘿
Hey.
记住
Remember.
不
No.
我会记住的
I'll remember.
我会记住
当我离开时
When I left,
我想过接管这星球上每个人的意念
I thought about taking over the minds of every human on this planet.
暴力、恐惧、贪婪
Violence, fear, greed,
全都没了
all gone.
为什么没做
Why didn't you?
因为没有了缺点
Because without their flaws,
他们就不是人类
they wouldn't be human.
拜托 诸克 你不能再留在这里
Please, Druig. You can't stay here anymore.
这些变异族想阻止我们杀死它们同类
These Deviants are trying to keep us from killing their own kind.
它们现在有了良知 因而更危险
They have a conscience now. That makes them more dangerous.
不 瑟希
No, Sersi.
这使它们成了我们
That makes them us.
永恒族与变异族
Eternals and Deviants.
都是阿里瑟姆的孩子
Arishem's children.
但你要我控制一个天神族的意念
But you are asking me to take control of a mind of a Celestial.
我没有那种能力
I do not have that kind of power.
我们需要费斯托斯
We'll need Phastos.
祝你好运
Well, good luck.
他很久以前就放弃人类了
He gave up on humans a long time ago.
（1945年8月 广岛）
是我害的
I did this.
如果我的科技没帮助他们进步…
If my technology hadn't helped them advance...
诸克说得对
Druig was right.
我们的任务是一个错误
Our mission was a mistake.
这些人
These people...
他们不值得拯救
they're not worth saving.
费斯托斯
Oh, Phastos.
他们不值得拯救
They're not worth saving.
谢谢　-传过来
- Thanks. - Give me a good one.
好　-这边
- All right. - Over here.
再来…
And...
太棒了　-耶
Oh, that's great, man! - Yeah! - Yeah!
耶　-赞
- Oh, yeah! - Nice.
漂亮　-不错 准备 接好
Good one. All right, ready? Throw!
（今日 芝加哥）
差一点
Oh, so close.
爸比…你看　-好
Daddy, Daddy, watch this. Yeah, okay.
注意　-传过来…
Watch this. Let me see. Let me see it.
爸 我才刚开始学
Dad. I'm only a starter.
你好
Hi.
你好 有事吗
- Hello. Can we help you?
再来
- Throw it again.
嘿 杰克 班
Hey, Jack. Ben.
你们好 他们是我大学同学
Hey, guys. These are my friends from college.
这是希薇亚和艾萨克 他是艾萨克
Uh, this is Sylvia and, uh, Isaac. That's Isaac.
艾萨克　-爸 他是超人
Isaac. Dad, that's Superman.
爸 他是超人　-杰克 你真搞笑
Dad, that's Superman! Jack... That's really funny, Jack.
不 他是超人　-他绝对不是超人
No, no! He is Superman. That is definitely not Superman.
我在电视上看过他 他在伦敦打怪兽
I saw him on TV. He was in London, fighting a monster.
你穿着披风 眼睛射出激光光
And you were with a cape and you were shooting laser beams out of your eyes.
我不穿披风的
- I don't wear a cape.
对不起　-好 我们该进去了
- Oh, sorry. Okay, well, we should just go inside, right?
能叫你克拉克吗 你现在当超人
Can I call you Clark? Is that what you go by now? Because, you know...
你叫过我更难听的
You've called me worse.
你懂了吗 杰克
- You got it, Jack?
这就对了
- Way to go. - Yes.
是　-好 做给我看
All right. Show me how it's done.
绕圈圈…
Round and round and round and round and round.
你会了 继续　-过来
Yep, you got it. Keep going. Come on.
对 一点也不做作
Yeah. Incredibly natural, guys.
所以 这么多年过去了
So, after all these years,
连你也相信艾贾克的谎言
even you fell for Ajak's lies.
没必要在伤口上洒盐
No need to rub it in.
她不让我们干涉人类冲突是有道理的
It all makes sense why she wouldn't let us interfere with human conflicts.
冲突引发战争
Conflicts lead to war,
战争促进科技与医药进步
and war actually leads to advancement in lifesaving technology and medicine.
我们的任务始终都不是
So our mission was never to
创造一个和平或和谐的世界
make a peaceful or harmonious world,
而是不计代价增加人口
but to increase the population at all costs.
把人类当天神族的食物 对吧
Just farming humans as food for the Celestials, right?
说得真无情
That's bleak.
告诉你的丈夫和孩子
Well, so is telling your husband and your child
他们可能在几天内死去也是
that they could be dead within a few days.
我以为你已经放弃了人类了
Thought you'd given up on humans.
我很幸运 懂吗
I got lucky. Okay?
我现在有一个家庭
I have a family now.
他们再次给了我信心
They give me faith again.
我每天都在他们身上看到人类的优点
And I see the good in humanity in them every single day.
听好 我帮不了你们
So, look, I cannot help you.
我绝不离开他们　-费斯托斯
I am never leaving them. Phastos...
对不起 瑟希
I'm sorry, Sersi.
不先考虑后果
It was wrong for me to use my powers
就使用我的超能力是错的
without thinking about the consequences in the first place.
我选择用双手修理孩子的自行车
So, now, I choose to use my hands to fix my child' bicycle, okay?
是吗
Do you?
我不再使用我的超能力了
I don't use my powers anymore.
你确定
You sure?
你…
What are you...
你有病啊 我的孩子就在隔壁房间
What the hell is wrong with you? My child is right down the hallway!
那看来像有人一直在使用超能力
That looks like someone's been using his powers.
天啊　-你打造了坚不可摧的藏身处
Oh, my God. I bet you've built the perfect safe house.
这什么做的 汎合金吗
What is this even made of? - Vibranium?
不要
- Don't!
秋季系列
Fall collection.
IKEA
IKEA.
混蛋
Ass.
五千多年来你如何忍受这家伙
How did you even deal with this guy for over 5,000 years?
留在这里 还不如请变异族来吃饭
If you stay here, you might as well invite the Deviants to dinner.
不用等什么世界末日了
Never mind waiting for the end of the world.
他说得有道理
He has a point.
抱歉 你不能突然出现就要我跟你走
No, I'm sorry. You can't just show up in my life and expect me to go with you.
我不会…　-你应该去 亲爱的
I'm not gonna... You should go, habibi.
你要我去
You want me to go?
你知道我妈会怎么对你说吧
You know what my mom would say to you right now, right?
别拖了 菲尔 好好处理你的事
Quit procrastinating, Phil, and take care of your business.
他是慢郎中
He's a chronic procrastinator.
我不会离开你们两个 免谈
I'm not leaving you two. No way.
我也不乐意
I'm not happy about it,
但如果有机会看着杰克长大
but if there's a chance for us to watch Jack grow up to live a life of his own,
我们就该把握
we should take it.
（伊拉克）
多摩号
The Domo.
哇
Wow.
空气中弥漫着不祥的气氛
A foreboding atmosphere fills the air.
诡异的寂静使我们的肺窒息
An eerie stillness chokes our lungs.
干嘛 你吓到我们了 知道吧
What are you doing? You know you're creeping us out. You know that, right?
天啊 拜托冷静
Oh, God! Stay calm, T, please!
薯片 只是薯片
Chips. It's just chips.
如你所见 永恒族也有人类的情绪
As you can see, being an Eternal does not preclude you from having human emotions
比如胆小如鼠
such as cowardice.
她做了什么
What has she done?
那是我实验室的石棺吗
Is that... a sarcophagus in my lab?
这是玛卡瑞 还是该叫她囤积女王
This is Makkari. Or should I say Miss Havisham?
我们有几世纪没见到她了
None of us have seen her for centuries.
准备回家了吗
Ready to go home?
那是乌木之刃吗
Is that the Ebony Blade?
圣剑
Excalibur.
亚瑟一直很煞你
Arthur always did have a crush on you.
所以你是说…
So you mean...
我等了几世纪想回奥林匹亚星
I've been waiting for centuries to go back to Olympia,
现在你却跟我说
and now you're telling me...
它不存在
...it doesn't exist?
对 还有世界要毁灭了
That, and the world is ending.
我的无聊时光终于要结束了
At last my boredom is ending.
你看过我的电影吗
Have you seen my movies?
我没有DVD播放机
I don't have a DVD player.
DVD
DVD?
现在大家都看串流
It's all about streaming now.
你需要一台Kindle
You know, what you need is a Kindle.
知道那是什么吗 就像…
Do you know what that is? It's like a...
我刚发觉如果你不知道iPad
You know, I just realized that if you don't know what an iPad is,
几乎没办法解释
there's almost no way to explain it.
那你最后是如何取得《翠玉录》的
So, how did you end up scoring this Emerald Tablet,
美丽的玛卡瑞
my beautiful, beautiful Makkari?
你想我吗
Miss me?
请问这怎么回事
I'm sorry, what are we watching? Because this...
新发展吗 我不喜欢　-你们俩…
Is this new? Because I hate it. Are you two...
费斯托斯
Phastos,
我得控制一个天神族的意念
I need to control the mind of a Celestial.
好 准备好
Okay, get ready for it.
手环
Bracelets?
你帮我们做了手环
You made us bracelets?
以下是天神族的基本介绍
So, here's a little Celestial 101.
天神族是宇宙中最强大的能量生产者
Celestials are the most powerful energy generators in the universe.
阿里瑟姆创造我们时
When Arishem made us,
为我们注入了无限的宇宙能量
he imbued us with infinite cosmic energy
使我们身体不断再生
to keep our bodies regenerating.
这些手环理论上…
The bracelets, in theory,
会关闭我们的再生过程
shut down our regeneration process.
于是我们身体会累积额外的宇宙能量
And once that happens, our bodies accumulate extra cosmic energy.
要做什么
What for?
如果变异族能吸取我们的能量
Well, if the Deviants can absorb our energy,
要是我们也能吸取彼此的能量呢
what if we can absorb each other's energy as well?
如果我能设法连结我们所有人
If I can find a way to connect us all,
我们其中一人就能变得无比强大
one of us could become immensely powerful,
汇集其他人的累积能量
pulling the accumulated energy from the rest,
形成…
forming...
一个统一意念
a Uni-Mind.
统合为一的意念
"Uni" meaning "one," "mind" meaning "mind."
我们第一次就听懂了
Oh, no, we heard you the first time.
烂名字　-我们脑力激荡…
- Terrible name. - We'll brainstorm...
「脑力激荡」
"Brainstorm"!
这名字好多了　-不 是我发明的
That's a way better name! No, I invented it,
我想叫什么都行
so I'm calling it whatever I want.
假设诸克能让蒂亚穆睡着
So suppose Druig can, say... put Tiamut to sleep--
然后呢
Then what?
我们为人类在另一个星球上找新家
We find humans a new home on another planet.
还要建造大船 每种动物带两只走
Are we building a big ship, too? Take a pair of each animal?
什么无法拯救世界呢 你的酸言酸语
Well, you know what's never saved the planet? Your sarcasm.
太空殖民可能花上好几十年
Space colonization could take decades.
有我们帮助的话会很快
It can happen quickly with our help.
要是不小心杀死蒂亚穆呢
What if we end up accidentally killing Tiamut?
我们可能要为全宇宙
We could be responsible for billions of lives
没创造出来的数十亿生命负责
not being created across the universe.
老大 我说得对吗
Boss, am I right?
说句话 伊卡利斯
Say something, Ikaris.
你认为我们不应该这样做
You don't think we should be doing this.
艾贾克选择瑟希来领导我们
Ajak chose Sersi to lead us.
应该由瑟希决定
Sersi should decide.
别管艾贾克选了谁
Forget who Ajak chose.
你是最强的 应该由你做这个决定
You're the strongest. You should be making this decision.
好 继续自欺欺人吧
Fine. Just keep lying to yourself.
丝派克
Sprite.
好 这不是…
Okay, this is not...
伊卡利斯　-别去追他
Ikaris. Don't run after him.
金勾 我…你们
Kingo, I... You guys.
别担心 丝派克总是怪里怪气的
Hey. Don't sweat it. Sprite's always cranky.
即使她不在 我也常听到她抱怨
I used to hear her complaining even when she wasn't there.
我没事 金勾
I'm okay, Kingo.
如果你认为该这么做 我相信你
If you think we should do this, I trust you.
我会像往常一样一路追随你
I will follow you to the end, like I always have.
你说什么
What did you say?
我会像往常一样一路追随你
I will follow you to the end, like I always have.
我不是你以为的那样
I'm not who you think I am.
（六天前 南达科他州）
我们还有多久时间
How long do we have?
七天
Seven days.
很好
Good.
我们完成任务了
We completed our mission.
她在哪
Where is she?
伦敦
London.
过着美好的生活
She has a good life there.
我确定她很想你
I'm sure she's missed you.
如果回到她身边 我就会告诉她真相
If I'd gone back to her, I would only have told her the truth.
她会很痛苦
She would've suffered
知道她所爱的世界有一天会毁灭
knowing this world she loves would end one day.
伊卡利斯
Ikaris.
我们必须告诉他们真相
We have to tell them the truth.
什么
What?
为什么 　-因为同心协力
Why? Because together
我们也许能阻止神现
we might be able to stop the emergence.
阻止神现
"Stop the emergence"?
听好
Listen...
我知道最后很难…　-听我说
Ajak, I know it's hard at the end...Listen to me, Ikaris.
我追随阿里瑟姆数百万年
I have followed Arishem for millions of years.
从来没有怀疑过他
And I have never doubted him.
直到现在　-为什么是现在
Until now. Why now?
为什么是现在
Why now?
五年前 萨诺斯消灭了宇宙一半人口
Five years ago, Thanos erased half of the population of the universe.
造成神现延宕
Delayed the emergence.
但这个星球的人…
But the people of this planet
一弹指就把所有人救回来
brought everyone back with the snap of a finger.
在我让你们离开后
You know, after I let you all go,
我周游世界 生活在地球人之间
I traveled the world, living among them.
见过他们互斗、撒谎和杀戮
I have seen them fight and lie and kill,
但我也见到他们
but I have also seen them
欢笑与相爱
laugh and love.
我见到他们创造和梦想
I've seen them create and dream.
这个星球
This planet
以及这些人
and these people...
改变了我
have changed me.
阿里瑟姆设计的代价 不值得
The cost of Arishem's design, it's not worth it.
这次不值得
Not this time.
我相信你 艾贾克
I trust you, Ajak.
我会像往常一样
I'll follow you to the end,
一路追随你
as I always have.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们必须让所有人再度聚首
We have to bring everyone back together.
我得先给你看一样东西
There's something I have to show you first.
（阿拉斯加州）
就在前面
It's just up ahead.
它们一定困在冰里好几世纪
They must have been trapped in the ice for centuries
上周地核因神现而升温
and broke free last week when the glacier started to melt
冰川融化 它们才挣脱而出
as the Earth's core heats up for the emergence.
它们杀光整家钻油公司的工人
They killed an entire company of oil workers.
我追踪它们到这里
I tracked them here.
我怀疑你可能改变了主意
I suspected you might have changed your mind.
我不能让你背叛阿里瑟姆
I can't let you betray Arishem.
你何不亲手杀了我
Why don't you just kill me yourself?
等其他人意识到地球出事了
When the others realize something is happening to the Earth,
他们会来找你
they'll come to you.
等他们发现你的尸体
When they find your body,
就知道变异族回来了
they'll know the Deviants are back.
那会让他们忙到神现为止
It'll keep them busy until the emergence.
我一直对你忠心耿耿 艾贾克
I've been loyal to you, Ajak.
保守你的秘密几世纪
Kept your secret for centuries,
欺骗我在乎的所有人
lied to everyone I cared about,
但从未怀疑我为天神族效力的使命
but never have I doubted my purpose to serve the Celestials.
伊卡利斯
Oh, Ikaris.
我把你带上错误的路
I've led you down the wrong path.
这是我所知唯一的路
It's the only path I know.
我就想会在这里找到你
Thought I'd find you here.
我常想到这个地方
I've thought about this place a lot.
世事的变化真惊人
Amazing how things change over time.
也许改变的是我们
Maybe we're the ones who've changed.
我知道你不赞同我们的计划
I know you don't agree with our plan.
我一直认为天神族就像海洋
I've always thought of the Celestials like the ocean.
他们毫无偏见地赋予与夺取生命
They give life and they take life away without bias.
如果他们走了 宇宙末日终将来临
If they were gone, this universe would eventually end.
你想做的是让人类脱离自然秩序
What you're trying to do is free humanity from the natural order.
让整个星球的生命灭绝并不自然
It's not natural to allow all life on an entire planet to be destroyed.
阿里瑟姆的方法过时又暴力
Arishem's way is archaic and violent.
我不想吵架 瑟希
I don't want to fight, Sersi.
这一切很快就会结束
It'll all end soon.
只是没有尽头 是吗
Except there is no end, is there?
我们会继续前进 没有记忆
We'd carry on without our memories
没有自由意志
or free will
永远这样下去
for eternity.
你怕了
You're afraid.
我不介意离开这个世界
I wouldn't mind leaving this world.
我只愿当我们离开时
I only wish that when we do,
我能记得你
I would be able to remember you.
我爱上你了 瑟希
I'm in love with you, Sersi.
我很感激与你共度的岁月
I'm grateful for the life I've lived with you.
伊卡利斯
Ikaris.
瑟希
Sersi?
开始了
It's started.
不 天啊
Oh, no. My God.
统一意念呢
What about the Uni-Mind?
我还没想出连结我们的办法 但快了
I haven't figured out a way to connect us, but I'm close.
就差一点点　-还要多久
- I'm very, very close. - How much longer?
我不知道 瑟希
I don't know, Sersi!
找到神现点
Find the point of emergence.
你一直都知道末日将临
You always knew the end was coming.
那一定是种解脱
It must be a relief.
那个变异族还在追踪我们
That Deviant is still tracking us.
复仇不会给你平静 圣娜
Revenge won't bring peace for you, Thena.
但杀死它却可以
But killing it might.
伊卡利斯
Ikaris?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我希望你平静地离开这个世界
I wanted you to leave this world in peace.
对神现浑然不知
Without knowing about the emergence.
但我失败了
But I failed.
真希望艾贾克没有选择你
I wish Ajak hadn't chosen you.
我就快完成了
I'm close to figuring it out.
老大 你在做什么
Boss, what are you doing?
我让这件事拖够久了
I've let this go on long enough.
不要伤害他
Don't hurt him!
他骗我们
He lied to us.
他早已知道神现的事
He already knew about the emergence.
不 他不知道
No, he didn't.
离开巴比伦时 艾贾克全告诉我了
Ajak told me everything when we left Babylon.
什么
What?
你根本不打算让我们阻止神现
You were never gonna let us stop the emergence.
没错
No.
我只想保护你们不受变异族侵害
I only wanted to protect you from the Deviants.
艾贾克若要你接替她 为何选了我
If Ajak wanted you to take her place, why did she choose me?
你做了什么
What have you done?
他杀了她
He killed her.
我是不得已的
I had to.
她爱你啊
She loved you.
是吗 　-她爱你
- Did she? - She loved you.
你认为接受真相很容易吗
Do you think it was easy to live with the truth?
知道有一天这一切都会结束
To know that one day all this would end?
继续骗你们
To keep on lying to you?
如果我们给人类选择
If we gave humanity the choice,
他们多少人愿意死
how many of them would be willing to die
好让数十亿人诞生
so that billions more could be born?
我们不会给他们选择
We're not giving them a choice.
这就是你愿意杀人的原因吗
Is this why you're willing to kill?
你真可悲
You are so pathetic!
我是永恒族 费斯托斯
I'm an Eternal, Phastos.
我为阿里瑟姆而存在
I exist for Arishem.
你也一样
As do you.
那是你的本质
It's who you are.
我完全不会改变自己的本质
I wouldn't change a single thing about who I am.
无论先天或后天
Born or made.
但我不是为了阿里瑟姆而存在
But I do not exist for Arishem,
而是为我家人
I exist for my family!
那么你犯了和艾贾克一样的错误
Then you are making the same mistake Ajak did.
我找到蒂亚穆了
I found Tiamut.
不　-玛卡瑞
- No! - Makkari!
快离开
Get out of here!
金勾
Kingo.
你不能背叛你的家人
You do not turn against your family.
吉尔伽美什因你而死
Gilgamesh died because of you.
你们对付不了我
You won't succeed against me.
有必要的话 我会杀光你们
And I will kill every one of you if I have to.
等等
Wait.
我跟你走
I'm going with you.
丝派克
Sprite...
怎么了
What is this?
丝派克为什么跟伊卡利斯走
Why did Sprite go with Ikaris?
因为她爱他
Because she loves him.
你们没注意到吗
Oh, you guys didn't pick up on that?
他把我们耍得团团转
He really fooled us, didn't he?
卡伦 我们走
Karun, let's go.
等等 你想去哪里
Wait, where the hell are you going?
我帮不了你们
I can't help you guys.
我还是认为伊卡利斯是对的
I still think Ikaris is right.
就这样 你要跟他走
So, that's it, huh? Just gonna follow him?
我爱这个星球上的人
I love the people of this planet.
但如果你们阻止神现
But if you stop this emergence,
就会妨碍其他许多类似的世界
you are preventing so many other worlds like this one
被创造出来
from being created.
我依然相信阿里瑟姆
I still have faith in Arishem.
但不愿为我的信仰伤害你们任何人
But I refuse to hurt any of you for my beliefs.
我们需要你
We need you.
即使有我帮忙 我们也不是对手
Even with my help, we're no match.
那是伊卡利斯
It's Ikaris.
但…
But...
希望在下一个星球见到你们
I hope to see you on the next planet.
谢谢你们为了人类…
Thank you for all you've done...
所做的一切
...for humanity.
十分荣幸认识你们
It's been a great honor.
我会想念你们大家的
I will miss you all.
听着
Look,
就算要在对抗伊卡利斯时丧命
if I'm gonna get myself killed going up against Ikaris,
我们也需要一个备案
we'll need to have a backup plan.
我们所有的力量即使增强
All of our powers, even if they're amplified,
都不足以杀死一个天神族
are not enough to kill a Celestial, so...
瑟希把一个变异族变成一棵树
Well, Sersi did turn a Deviant into a tree.
你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
你不打算告诉我吗
You didn't wanna tell me that?
你以前根本做不到
You've never been able to do it before.
我不知道怎么发生的
I don't know how it happened, okay?
也很确定我无法再做到
And I'm pretty sure I couldn't do it again.
你不觉得现在该试试吗
Well, now is the time to try, don't you think?
费斯托斯 那个变异族死了
Phastos, that Deviant is dead.
我们计划让蒂亚穆睡着 不是杀了它
Our plan is to put Tiamut to sleep, not to kill it.
我不能杀死天神族
I can't kill a Celestial.
瑟希
Sersi. Sersi.
我们不能
We can't!
We can't.
没关系 瑟希
It's okay, Sersi.
让我来处理
I got this.
没时间懊悔了
There's no time for that.
我没看到谎言就在面前
I didn't see the lies right in front of me.
甚至不知道艾贾克为何选我来领导
I'm not even sure why Ajak chose me to lead.
我曾问过吉尔伽美什
I asked Gilgamesh once
他为什么选择保护我
why he chose to protect me.
他说
He said,
「当你深爱一样东西 就会保护它
"When you love something, you protect it.
那是世界上最自然的事」
"It is the most natural thing in the world."
从我们抵达那天起 你就爱着这些人
You have loved these people since the day we arrived.
所以现在没人比你更适合领导我们
So, there is no one better to lead us now than you.
瑟希
Sersi.
起来
Get up.
艾贾克选择你是有原因的
Ajak chose you for a reason.
瑟希
Sersi!
瑟希 我们需要你
Oh, Sersi. We need you!
我已经讲了那段话
I already gave that speech.
什么
What?
你…什么…
You did... What...
瑟希 你体内的那颗球
Sersi, the sphere inside of you,
在你和阿里瑟姆之间建立了连结
it creates a connection between you and Arishem.
也许我能重新运用它
Maybe I can repurpose it
建立连结 在…
and create a connection between, uh,
我们所有人之间
well, all of us.
那可以触发统一意念
And that can activate the Uni-Mind.
太好了　-是啊
Great. Yeah.
但是…
But, um...
我得从你身上把它取出来
I have to take it out of you.
好
Okay.
动手吧
Do it.
好
Okay.
不要害死她
Don't kill her.
圣娜
Thena...
动手
Do it.
有用吗
Will it work?
非成功不可
It has to.
很高兴你在这里
I'm glad you're here.
谢谢你 丝派克
Thank you, Sprite.
保护神现
Protect the emergence.
你真的要杀了他们
You're really gonna kill them?
诸克在哪里
Where's Druig?
他在忙
He's busy.
圣娜 别冲动
Thena, play nice.
你向来不必对抗我
You've never had to fight me.
但我想很久了
But I've always wanted to.
是该让神安眠了
It's time to put a god to sleep.
我五个世纪前就该这么做
I should've done this five centuries ago.
诸克死了
Druig's gone.
结束了
It's over.
费斯托斯
Phastos.
我必须设法阻止
I have to try and stop this.
我得更靠近蒂亚穆
I need to get closer to Tiamut.
牵制伊卡利斯　-我们掩护你
Keep Ikaris busy. We've got you.
去吧
Go.
够了
Enough.
圣娜 住手
Thena, stop!
为何要帮伊卡利斯
Why are you helping Ikaris?
不能让它吸取我们的力量
We can't let it absorb our powers.
为时已晚
Too late.
圣娜 它想激怒你 不要…
Thena, he's trying to goad you. Don't...
玛卡瑞
Makkari!
瑟希呢
Where's Sersi?
你总是低估她
You always did underestimate her.
想得美
Oh, no.
别急
Not so fast.
老大
Boss.
不知道你怎么想 感觉很爽吧
I don't know about you, but this is really satisfying, right?
放开我 费斯托斯 我不能让她动手
Let me go, Phastos! I can't let her do this!
我不认同
I don't think so.
我早就想折损你的威力了 伊卡利斯
I've been wanting to clip your wings for a long time, Ikaris!
圣娜
Thena.
你变了
Oh, you've changed.
你败坏了
You're broken.
受损
Damaged.
废了
Useless.
你无法保护他们任何一个
You can't protect any of them.
瑟希
Sersi.
你力量不够强 做不到
You're not powerful enough to do this.
你也不会
And you won't.
你不是杀手
You're not a killer.
也许我变了
Maybe I've changed.
这是真正的你吗 丝派克
And is this really who you are, Sprite?
你真愿意让这星球的人死光吗
Are you really willing to let everyone on this planet die?
对不起 瑟希
I'm sorry, Sersi.
我一直很羡慕你 瑟希
I've always envied you, Sersi.
你能变成他们继续生活
'Cause you get to live as one of them.
而我永远做不到
And I never could.
知道我为何讨厌和人类一起生活吗
You know why I hated living with humans?
他们让我想起我不知道自己要的东西
Because they reminded me of things I didn't even know I wanted.
因为他们 现在我想知道长大的感觉
Because of them, now I wanna know what it feels like to grow up.
恋爱的滋味
To fall in love.
拥有家庭的感觉
To have a family.
最后知道自己活过
And to know, in the end, I've lived.
现在都结束了
It's all over now.
我们可以在新的地方重新开始
We get to start over somewhere new.
好感人的真心话
Well, that was very moving.
诸克
Druig.
我做不到
I can't do this.
现在这是你的战争了
This is your fight now.
圣娜
Thena.
是我
It's me.
吉尔伽美什
Gilgamesh.
看着我
Look at me.
吉尔伽美什
Gilgamesh?
留在这里
Stay here.
说吧
Say it.
留下
Stay here.
你会没事的
You'll be okay.
把你的手给我
Give me your hand.
真可惜
Ah, it's a shame.
你和我
You and I,
我们只是一个神的工具
we're just tools of a god.
为杀戮而生
Built to kill.
圣娜
Thena.
记住
Remember.
我记得
I remember.
快啊 瑟希
Come on, Sersi.
快点
Come on.
很美吧
It's beautiful, isn't it?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道
I know.
怎么做
How?
你怎么做到的
How did you do it?
碰触蒂亚穆的手掌时
When I touched Tiamut's palm,
我感觉能量涌入体内
I felt energy surging into me.
蒂亚穆加入了我们的统一意念
Tiamut joined our Uni-Mind.
我一直在想
I always wondered how we survived
我们如何在其他星球毁灭后存活
the destruction of other planets that we were on.
就是在天神族出现时与其连结
By being connected to the Celestial as it emerged.
我们合而为一
We became one...
甚至包括伊卡利斯和丝派克
...even Ikaris and Sprite
都是因为蒂亚穆
all because of Tiamut.
他走了吗
Is he gone?
丝派克
Sprite.
我还有来自统一意念的能量
I still have energy from the Uni-Mind.
我能让你成为人类
I think I can make you human.
你想要的一切都可以拥有
All the things you said you wanted, you can have them.
但你的时间稍纵即逝 有一天你会死
But your time will be fleeting and you'll die one day.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready for that?
准备好了
I am.
印度洋上突然冒出一个庞然巨石
The sudden appearance of an enormous stone figure in the Indian Ocean
（两周后 南达科他州）
给当局留下的问题比答案多
has left more questions than answers for authorities.
美国和澳大利亚海军舰艇维持防御阵势
U.S. and Australian naval ships are maintaining defensive positions,
但在这个…
but at this...
那是你们干的
You guys did that?
我真的好爱你
I love you so much.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我有时会搞混
I get confused sometimes.
我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
爸说你是雅典娜女神
So, Dad said you're the goddess Athena.
圣娜 差两个字
"Thena." Drop the "A."
你有什么超能力
What's your superpower?
麻烦…等一下
Um, can you just... Look... One second.
好
Okay. All right.
那东西…好
See, that thing is... Okay.
她差点伤到你 是吧
Almost gave you a shave and a haircut, didn't she?
站在我后面
Stand behind me, actually.
记得怎么摀耳朵吗
Um, you remember earmuffs?
谢谢你
Remember how we practiced earmuffs? Thank you so much.
你打死都不准当保母了
You know that your babysitting privileges are completely revoked, right?
别靠近小孩子
Like, it's done.
谢谢 暴力…
Thank you. Violence... Hey.
暴力绝对不是答案 对吧 圣娜
Violence is never the answer.  Right, T?
一定要用大脑
You gotta always use your brain, hmm?
像你在沙滩上开打那样
Like you did fighting on the beach?
你老爸…
Your dad
冷静而坚定地对坏人晓以大义
spoke calmly and firmly to the bad guy and he had no choice
他别无选择只能听我的 所以没暴力
but to listen to me, so no violence.
这孩子十岁了
The kid is ten...
不是笨蛋
...not stupid!
你们何时走人
When are you guys leaving? When is that happening?
快了吧
That's happening soon, right?
诸克来了 别靠近他
Ah, yes, there's Druig.  Don't go anywhere near him.
好
Yeah!
杰克 到这边就好
Okay, that's far enough, Jack.
爸 多摩号超酷的
Wow, Dad, the Domo's so cool.
老爸徒手把它修好的
Your dad fixed that with his bare hands.
我们有一天也能上太空吗
Can we go to space, too, one day?
等你拿到学习驾照再说
Let's wait till you get your learner's permit, okay?
费斯托斯
Hey, Phastos.
保重了
Take care.
这个世界有你真幸运
This world is lucky to have you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道你不喜欢拥抱
I know you're not a hugger, so...
好
Okay.
你认为等我们找到其他永恒族
You think when we find the other Eternals out there,
他们会像我们一样接受真相吗
that they'll accept the truth the way we did?
因为真相会让他们自由
...because the truth will set them free.
我就说那玩意会上瘾
Told you that thing was addictive.
记得来找我哦
Please visit?
我尽量
I'll try.
放学后有空的话
When I get time off from school.
哇 待在人类环境中对你有好处
Oh, wow. Listen, it's gonna be good for you to be in a human environment.
你会学到一些社交技巧
You'll pick up some social skills.
你认为你不需要吗
Oh, you didn't think you needed those?
这也难怪
That explains so much.
我会想你的
Gonna miss you.
我也会
Me, too.
小姐
Madam.
谢谢你 卡伦
Thanks, Karun.
有时在想我们是否做对了
Sometimes I wonder if we did the right thing.
杀死蒂亚穆
Killing Tiamut.
后悔也来不及了
It's too late for that.
但你是跟着感觉走
But you followed your heart.
我们都是
We all did.
连伊卡利斯也是
Even Ikaris.
看来有人在等你
Looks like someone's waiting for you.
他本人帅多了
He's a lot cuter in person.
现在你还不能把我变长颈鹿吗
So, after all that, you still can't change me into a giraffe?
下次在神现时与天神族连结
Well, I could next time I'm connected to a Celestial
并执行统一意念时就可以
during an emergence whilst performing a Uni-Mind.
听上去是不行
Yeah. That sounds like a "no" to me.
现在你怎么办
What'll you do now?
不确定
Not sure.
这个星球是我的家 但是…
This planet's my home, but...
我不能再假装成人类了
I can't pretend to be human anymore.
我爱你 瑟希
I love you, Sersi.
不管你是什么
I don't care what you are.
记得我们说过不再有秘密吗
Remember when we talked about no more secrets?
我没有秘密了 我保证
I have no more secrets, I promise.
其实
Actually,
我有个秘密想告诉你
I have one I want to tell you.
什么
What is it?
原来我的家族史…
It turns out my family history is...
很复杂
complicated.
瑟希
Sersi?
瑟希 怎么了
Sersi, what's wrong?
瑟希
Sersi?
Sersi!
你选择牺牲一个天神族
You have chosen to sacrifice a Celestial
为了这个星球的人
for the people of this planet.
我会饶了他们
I will spare them,
但你的记忆会显示他们是否值得活
but your memories will show if they are worthy to live.
我会回来进行审判
And I will return for judgment.
你还好吗 泰德
You all right, Ted?
你看到了吗
Did you see that?
（胡迪尼 亲自登台）
永恒族
已经好几个星期了
It's been weeks.
我们没有他们任何人的消息
We haven't heard from any of them.
就好像…
It's like...
他们消失了
they've disappeared.
阿里瑟姆
Arishem.
我们必须回去
We have to go back.
我也感觉到了
I feel it, too.
怎么了
What?
哇
Wow.
我的耳朵和眼睛都麻掉了
Aah! My ears. My eyes are numb.
不再为你们酒醉瞬间移动了
No more drunk teleporting for you.
等一下…
Hang on, hang on.
请看
Behold,
泰坦星的王子
the royal prince of Titan,
萨诺斯的弟弟 红心骑士
brother of Thanos, the Knave of Hearts,
击败了…
defeater...
萨诺斯的弟弟
Thanos' brother?
黑罗伯特　-罗杰
...of Black Robert... Roger.
击败了黑罗杰
Defeater of Black Roger.
伟大的冒险家
The great adventurer,
神秘星球的星狐
Starfox of Mystery Planet.
很高兴认识你们
What a pleasure to make your acquaintance,
永恒族的同胞们
my fellow Eternals.
你不必每次都来全套的
You know, you really don't have to do the whole thing every time.
你所做的一切令人赞叹
Everything you do is impressive.
全都要讲一遍　-我知道
What am I gonna leave off the list? No, I know it's impressive.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是厄洛斯
I'm Eros.
这是皮普
This is Pip.
你和传说中的一样美 圣娜
And you are as beautiful as legends say, Thena.
你们想干什么
What do you want, lads?
皮普和我是来帮忙的 对不对
Pip and I are here to help, aren't we?
你们的朋友麻烦大了
Your friends are in big trouble.
我们知道去哪里找他们
And we know where to find them.
翻译：Aaron Wu
你做得到
You can do this.
死亡对我来说是奖赏
Death is my reward.
（死亡对我来说是奖赏）
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我得试试看
I have to try.
你真的准备好了吗 惠特曼先生
Sure you're ready for that, Mr. Whitman?
《永恒族》将再回归…
请点击www.osdb.link/9h4d9评价此字幕帮助其他人选择最佳字幕